Arik Rahaman Anoy

Summary

Experienced Developer skilled in developing any kind f website and front end developing. And customize any kind of WordPress website. And also expert in bug fixing.

Skills

HTML / CSS/ Front end developing JavaScript / jQuery/ WordPress

Experience

Hire4Hired / 05/2019 to Present

Senior Web Developer

- Managed the general maintenance of the website on a daily basis, supporting servers that saw over 20,000 unique visitors per day.
- Led the website redesign that came with the company's rebranding efforts, requiring a complete rebuild of the website from the foundation with the addition of a new shopping cart and complex shipping and tax calculations.
- Integrated and updated a map functionality for the website .
- Assisted with the upload and placement of product images, information pages, recipe cards and other key elements that accompanied the rebranding and website redesign for the company.
- Update the website with newly design and comfort to use and maintain webpage speed.

Any2text Media / 03/2018 to Present

Web Developer

- Monitoring and continuously optimizing web security applications, ultimately bringing hacker attacks down from 2.7% to under 0.003%.
- Designing and redesigning the core pages of the e-commerce store while collaborating with the sales and marketing team to increase simplicity and, in turn, increase cart conversion rates to 22%.
- Working with content creators to implement new content on the main website and blog, ensuring that new content types (including articles, podcasts and videos) are styled properly for quick and easy viewing.
- Fixing bugs across the website and its front-end, and maintaining it on a day-to-day basis to ensure seamless functioning.
- Fixing the HTML/CSS code and monthly update.

Additional Information

Languages: English, Bengali **Hobbies**: Playing, Problem

solving, Teaching **Certificate**: Udemy,

ProgrammingHub , Solo Learn **Year of experience** : 1year+

Education

High school: Grade 7 Jahanara Israil school & Dilege 01/2001 to Present

Minor: Communications

Certifications

udemy - HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
ProgrammingHub _ HTML5 , CSS3
SoloLearn- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery